《越狱》前情提要K
Previously on Prison Break:
-牧场不见了，麦可 -我们得想个办法
- The ranch is gone, Michael. - We gotta do something.
-不要伤害任何人 -我有办法了
- It's not gonna involve hurting anyone. - I got an idea.
抱歉打扰你，女士 你家有停电吗？
Sorry to bother you, ma'am. Is your electricity out?
那些逃犯就在其中一座城镇里
Those cons are in one of these towns.
不可能超过 方圆64里的地区
They couldn't have gone further than 64 miles in any direction.
我要这地区内所有的消息
I want everything in that perimeter.
说真的 我以为我是来向总统呈报
You know, to be honest, I was expecting to brief the president.
从现在起你向我回报
You report to me now.
坦白说，现在最大的问题
Frankly, the biggest issue we have to address...
就是令嫒可能面临的刑责
...are the charges facing your daughter.
很荣幸见到你，先生
Pleasure to meet you, sir.
莎拉，记得我去找你时 和你在一起的男人？
Sara, did you remember that guy that I met with you in your apartment?
我要你离他远一点
I want you to stay away from him.
-你在说什么？ -我还发现了其他事
- What are you talking about? - I found out some other things too,
-那是哪里？ -是荷兰
- Where is that? - Oh, it's Holland.
真美丽
It's beautiful.
把车子的油加满 一小时后回来会合
Gas up the car. And we'll meet you right back here in an hour.
好
Okay.
双手抱头，跪下
Put your hands behind your head and drop to your knees.
-天啊K -不准发出声音，你这老婊
- Oh, God. - Don't say a word, you old whore.
否则我割断你的喉咙
Or I'm gonna cut your throat out.
你敢再叫，我就把 喉咙里的声带挖出来
You try that again, I'll pry those vocal cords right out of your throat.
她要上来了
She's coming up.
她要做什么？
What's she doing?
她要上来了
She's coming up here.
留在那里，留在那里
Stay there, stay there.
妈，你在家吗？
Hey, Mom, you home?
不要妄动，保持安静
Stay here. Stay quiet.
妈？
Mom?
-不要激动K -放开她，把双手举高
- It's okay. It's okay. - Back away and put your hands up.
-别激动 -休想
- Just go easy. - Go nothing.
现在王牌不在她的手上
She ain't the one carrying the cards here.
放开她，把双手举高
Back away and put your hands up.
我要割断她的颈静脉 才会把手举高
I put my hand up, I'm gonna take her jugular with it.
大家都别做傻事好吗？
I don't want anyone to do anything stupid, okay?
不准动！
Don't move.
我们文明一点
Let's be civil.
别挣扎，就是这样
Stop, relax. Here you go.
园艺店老板说 柏劳力大无穷
Guy at the garden center said Burrows was strong as a gorilla.
（犹他州图尔警局）
TooELE, UTAH TooELE PoLICE DEPARTMENT
-他们在下午一点被绑起来 -他指认出两人
- It was 1 p.m. When they tangled it up. - The guy ID'd both of them.
史柯菲和柏劳 他非常肯定
Scofield, Burrows. No doubt about it in his mind.
既然是下午一点 两人可能已逃到三百里外了
That was 1 p.m., they could be 300 miles from here by now.
店里被偷走许多 十字镐、铲子和电动工具
You have picks, shovels and power tools missing from that store.
他们还在，他们在挖掘
They're here and they're digging.
图尔的街道下 埋着五百万美金？
Five million dollars buried somewhere beneath the streets of Tooele.
-你真的相信这种事？ -他们相信
- You really believe that? - They believe that.
这是重点
And that's the important thing.
我们无从找起 我们没有人力家家户户去调查
They could be anywhere now. We don't have the units to go door to door.
我们不需要人力
And we won't need them.
他会告诉我们从哪里找起
He's gonna tell us where to look.
片名：越狱风云
剧名：埋藏
（伊利诺州，芝加哥）
真巧，我正想传简讯给你
It's so funny, I was just about to text you.
-今天是你的幸运日 -是吗？
- Today's your lucky day. - Is it?
对，我的麦欣阿姨终于给了我 她有名的巧克力碎片饼干做法
Yeah, my Aunt Maxine finally gave me her famous chocolate-chip-cookie recipe.
你今晚有空的话 我想请你第一个试吃
And if you're free tonight, I'd love for you to be my guinea pig.
我今晚没空
I can't. Not tonight.
别这样，你听起来跟丹尼尔一样 “今晚没空K”
Come on. You sound just like Daniel, "Not tonight. Not tonight."
你不介意的话，我得走了
You know what? If you don't mind, I've actually gotta go.
你没事吧？你的推车是空的K
Are you okay? I mean, your cart's empty...
我没事，只是得走了
I'm good. Yeah, I just gotta go.
莎拉K
Sara...
-所有能出差错的都出了差错 -太糟了，我们不能这样
- This is going wrong in every possible way. - This is stupid, man. We cannot do this.
现在覆水难收了
Hat's over the wall now.
你这话是什么意思？
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
我们作了决定
I mean we committed.
该是拿钱的时候
It's time to go get the hat.
-我们别无选择 -有选择的
- We don't have a choice. - Yeah, we do.
我们可以现在就离开这里
We can walk right up out of here right now, man.
然后怎样？
And then what?
我们已经进了屋里
We are already in the house.
这些女人被绑起来 我们已犯下这宗罪行
Those women are bound. We have already committed this crime.
就算离开也不会改变情况
We leave, it ain't gonna change any of that.
为什么这个青贮窖 不能出现在四下无人的地方？
Why couldn't there just be a silo in the middle of a field with no one around?
我们可以想办法 去别的地方筹钱
We'll figure it out and get the money another way.
对，也许我可以再去抢银行
Yeah, maybe I can rob another bank.
查理曾经对我说过一句话
You know what Charles once said to me?
他说犯了罪，一辈子都是犯人
He said there's no such thing as an ex-con.
因为我以前还认为 我们可以洗清犯下的罪行
Because I used to think there was a way we could wipe the slate clean.
弥补我们的罪恶
Make up for everything we've done.
现在已经覆水难收，林克
The hat's over the wall, Linc.
大家都无法回头了
For everyone.
我知道现在道歉于事无补
Sorry isn't gonna mean anything to you right now.
但是我还是要说
But I wanna say it anyway.
现在的情况不在计划之中
This wasn't supposed to happen.
我们顶多一两小时就会离开
One or two hours, tops, and we'll be out of here.
我保证，我们不会伤害你们
You have my word, no one will harm you.
盯好她们
Keep your eyes open, okay?
千万不能让她们受伤害
Nothing happens to them.
绝对不能
Nothing.
（伊利诺州，芝加哥）
女医生起疑了
The doctor is suspicious.
这很正常 你出现时她正在和州长通话
She should be. She was on the line with the governor when you walked up.
你在监听
You were listening.
两条线都装了窃听器 我们又不是新手
Both lines are tapped, We're not rookies,
她父亲是否有告诉她发现什么？
Did her father tell her what he found?
电话上没有说
Not over the phone.
但是他知道你的身分
But he knows who you are.
她也知道了
And so does she,
看来透过她找到史柯菲 最后找到柏劳K
seeing how she was supposed to lead you to scofield and Burrows...
-这方法已经是死路一条 -不见得
...we're back to square one. - Not necessarily.
-他们还有其他关心的人 -那个孩子
- There are other people they care about, - The kid.
罗杰
L.J.
-州长的事，比尔K -保罗，专注在柏劳的儿子身上
- Now, in terms of the governor, Bill... - The Burrows kid, Paul.
专心点
Focus.
丹奎迪州长办公室，请稍等
Governor Tancredi's office, please hold.
-州长办公室，请稍等 -我父亲在吗？克莉丝
- Governor Tancredi's office. Hold, please. - Is my father in, Chris?
-稍等一下 -好
- Just a second. - Okay.
-丹奎迪州长办公室 -布鲁斯
- Governor Tancredi's office. - Hey, Bruce.
-你好，莎拉 -我想找我爸
- Oh, hi, sara. - I'm trying to get Dad.
-我要打他的手机联络 -他刚下飞机
- I need to reach him on his cell. - He just landed.
-应该很快就到家 -好
- Should be home soon. - Okay.
-不过他应该没心情和你谈 -为什么？
- Don't know if he'll be in a talking mood. - Why?
白宫打电话给你父亲 撤销了他的提名
Your father got a call from the White House. They withdrew his nomination.
什么？两小时前我才跟他通过电话 他没有提到
What? I talked to him two hours ago. He didn't say anything about that.
刚刚才通知的 他们说批准过程有困难
It just happened. According to them, his confirmation was going to be a problem.
-他有支持票不是吗？ -绝大多数支持
- We had the votes, right? - Supermajority.
所以笃定当选的人 被雷诺兹总统拒绝
Okay, so President Reynolds pulled the plug on a sure thing...
好让一切归零？
...in order to start over from scratch?
政治圈常发生这种事吗？
How often does something like that happen in politics?
从来没发生过
Never.
我们怎么会变成绑架犯？ 这是不对的
Since when did we become kidnappers? It ain't right.
我们明天再用钱 把良知买回来吧
Well, we can buy a conscience tomorrow.
是啊，闭上眼也无法忘记这件事
Yeah, well, yeah, closing your eyes ain't gonna make it go away.
我宁愿得到能控制的五分钟
I'll take five minutes of a situation I can control...
也不要不知所措的50年
...over 50 years of one I can't, any day.
百元钞票先生
Hey, Mr. Hundred Dollar Bill.
和非洲人同类是什么感觉？
What's it like being with the African persuasion, anyhow, huh?
-闭上你的嘴 -说到你的痛处了
- Yo, shut the hell up. - Oh, hit me a nerve.
-你为何不下来帮忙挖？ -你退后一点吧，黑兄弟？
- Why don't you get in that hole and dig? - How about you backing up, dark fella?
你在这里人生地不熟，白垃圾
You're a long way away from home, Trailer Park.
我可以把你丢进洞里
I can put you in that hole.
-没人听得到你叫救命 -够了
- And nobody would ever hear you scream. - Knock it off.
我们今天请到 保全专家马克伯奈
We have security expert Mark Bruni with us,,,
他将解释为何其他监狱
,,, who will explain how other prisons are ensuring,,,
不会再出现新的 福克斯河八人帮
,,, that they are not victimized by the next Fox River Eight,
应该是福克斯河七人帮 亚布兹已经撒手归西
should be the Fox River seven now that Abruzzi's taken his dirt nap.
当然了，愿他安息
God rest the man's soul, of course.
说到人数，我们少了一个人
Speaking of numbers, we're short one.
那小子去加油也花太久时间了吧
Kid's taking a long time to fill that gas tank up.
我已经用尽各种方法逼他
I leaned on him in every way I can think of.
他就是不开口
He's not talking.
你是天主教徒吗？
Are you Catholic?
这宗教不太好，有很多罪恶
Not much good in it. A lot of guilt.
不过唯一的好处 就是告解
But the one good thing is confession.
不管心里有什么让你难受 你只管说出来就好
Whatever you got eating at you, you just give it up.
我得承认，这种感觉很不错
Feels good, I have to say.
我想是因为说出来
Guess it's letting it out.
-让另一个人听你告解 -我无话可说
- Letting another human being hear... - I got nothing to say to you, man.
如果我告诉你一件事呢？
What if I told you something?
一个无人知晓的秘密
A secret nobody else knows.
奥斯卡席尔斯
Oscar shales.
他是我几年前追捕的逃犯
A guy I was chasing a few years back.
精明的不得了
Smart as hell.
我总是慢他一步
I kept just missing him.
过程变得像比赛，仿佛下西洋棋
It became kind of a game, like chess.
要不是他在逃亡时不断杀人
Would've been fun if it weren't for the fact...
老实说，过程其实很有趣
...that he were killing people all along the way.
受害者不断增加 我开始觉得都是我的错
Bodies kept stacking up, and I started to feel that it was because of me.
因为我不称职
Because I couldn't do my job.
因为我不够聪明
Because I wasn't smart enough.
我一直没抓到他
Never did catch him.
但是过程中我失控了
But I did lose it.
晚上开车时，我会看见东西
Saw things when I would drive at night.
看到尸体
Bodies.
做恶梦做到我无法入睡
Nightmares to the point that I couldn't sleep.
我完全和现实脱节
It was a complete break from reality.
所以我才需要吃这些药
That's what these little guys are for.
让我能继续办案
Keep me in the game.
我已经一吐为快 告诉你了
So now you know. Now it's off my chest.
你也应该试试看
Ought to try it sometime.
我已经说过了
Like I said before...
我无话可说
...I ain't gonna tell you nothing.
你知道他们在哪里
You know where those guys are.
如果你要我当抓耙子，你就找错人了
If you're looking for a rat, you've got the wrong guy, man.
不，我只是想让你 少承受点罪恶
No, I'm just trying to spare you some guilt.
包威逃狱后不到24小时 就杀害了第一个人
Bagwell was free less than 24 hours before he killed his first victim.
如果你不说出他的下落 他会继续杀人
If you don't tell me where he is now, he's gonna kill again.
这个罪都会怪在你的头上
And that blood is gonna be on your conscience and nobody else's.
告解也许不是件坏事，不是吗？
Confession might not be such a bad thing, huh?
（亚利桑那州京曼 克利普顿拘留所）
他刚到，罗杰
He just arrived, L.J.
不可能
That's impossible.
我事先没有预定和律师见面
I don't have a meeting scheduled with my lawyer.
他是伊利诺州法院 指派的公设辩护人
He's a court-appointed public defender in Illinois.
他不可能事先没通知我 就来亚利桑那
I doubt he would come to Arizona without calling me.
走吧
Let's go.
请说
Yeah?
在亚利桑那的柏劳的儿子 已处理好了
We're all set in Arizona with the Burrows kid,
很好
Good.
这小孩解决了
The kid's as good as gone,
你说律师叫什么名字？
What'd you say the name of that lawyer was?
没有告诉我，他告诉了典狱长
Didn't give it to me. Gave it to the warden.
那我要见监狱长 你有听到吗？
Then I want to talk to the warden. Hey, you hear me?
之后再去
After.
你好，罗杰
Hello, L.J.
-你想做什么？ -他们没说我的来意？
- What do you want? - They didn't tell you why I came here?
没有
No.
我是莫哈维郡这里的 助理检察官
I'm an ADA here in Mojave County.
我是来送文件给你的
I'm here to serve you with these.
那是什么？
What are those?
你的释放书
Your release papers.
（伊利诺州芝加哥，州长官邸）
-丹奎迪小姐 -你好，我爸在吗？
- Hey. Is my dad in? - Ms. Tancredi.
-他在书房里 -好，谢谢
- In the study. - Great, thank you.
爸？
Dad?
救命
Help!
我需要吃药
I need my pills.
拜托，我需要吃药
Please, I need my pills.
-什么事？ -我需要吃药
- What? - I need my pills.
-不可能 -你不了解，我一定要吃药
- Forget it. - No, you don't understand. I need them.
为了我的胎儿
They're for my baby.
那是甲福明 可以预防流产，拜托
They're Metformin, to prevent a miscarriage. Please.
药在厨房的抽屉里
They're in the drawer in the kitchen.
那个抽屉
That one right there.
-多少颗？ -两颗
- How many? - Two.
还有水，麻烦你
And water. Please.
-我要把布条塞回去 -等等
- Now I gotta put the gag back on. - Wait.
我还有一个问题要问你
Before you do, I just have one more question.
你看起来像个好人
You seem like a really good guy.
为何要这么做？
Why are you doing this?
我不是好人
I'm not a good guy.
你认为这些改变真的可以关住K
And these changes, do you really think they'll help keep predators,,,
包威这种危险人物吗？
,,, like Theodore Bagwell safely behind bars?
这是无庸置疑的K
Without a doubt,
我这张照片看起来像反社会人士
Picture makes me look like a sociopath.
我不是开玩笑，白垃圾 下来帮忙挖
I'm not joking with you, Trailer Park. Now, get in here and dig.
我现在残废，都要感谢各位的恩赐
I am incapable, thanks to all y'all.
记住，这地点是我找到的 不要忘了
Just remember, my X marked the spot! You remember that.
我们有更大的问题，那小伙子
We got a bigger issue. The kid.
-他离开多久了？ -有一小时半吧
- How long's it been since he left? - An hour and a half, maybe.
花一小时半加油？肯定出事了
An hour and a half to fill a tank of gas? That ain't right.
罗杰柏劳 涉及的双尸命案K
There has been a breaking development in the double-homicide prosecution,,,
出现了重大突破
,,, of Lincoln Burrows, Jr,
由于关键的血液和 指纹证据无故消失K
Due to the sudden disappearance of crucial blood,,,,
林克，我不知道你有个儿子
Hey, Linc, I didn't know you had a boy.
少了凶器 库克郡检察官别无选择
- The cook county District Attorney's Office had no choice,,,
只好撤销所有 对这名16岁少年的控诉
,,, but to drop all charges against the 16-year-old,
柏劳目前被关在K
Burrows is scheduled to be released,,,
亚利桑那州京曼的 克利普顿拘留所
,,, from the Klipton Detention center in Kingman, Arizona,,,
并预计明天早上释放出狱
,,, where he's currently being held, tomorrow morning,
她的车钥匙在哪里？
Keys to her car. Where are they?
-这里 -等一下好吗？
- Here. - Just hold on, okay?
-你不能这样做 -为什么？
- You can't do this, Linc. - Why not?
-林克，我们就快挖到了 -这话你已经说四小时了
- We are five minutes away in there. - We've been five minutes for four hours.
-再给我点时间，耐心一点 -你以为我在乎钱吗？
- Just give me some time. Be patient. - You think I give a damn about the money?
-那是必要的资源 -你是害怕失败
- I'm doing what's necessary. - You're afraid to fail.
你怕你的伟大计划会失败
You're afraid this plan ain't gonna work.
你想为了证明自己而被捕，随便你
You wanna get caught proving you can pull this off, be my guest.
罗杰出狱了，我一定要去找他
L.J.'s out there. I'm gonna get him.
我们横跨全国一千五百里 来到这里
We have come 1500 miles across country.
都已经走到这一步了
We have made it this far.
也许现在我们是该分开了
Then I guess this is where we part ways.
（FBI办公室 伊利诺州，芝加哥）
- Any word on the interrogation? - No, the kid's still stonewalling.
-侦讯有新消息吗？ -没有，那小子还在反抗
不过确定了 帕托西克的行踪
But we've got confirmation on Patoshik.
那位老妇人家中 到处是他的指纹
His prints were all over that old lady's house.
他没有偷走现金和珠宝
So he leaves the cash and the jewelry.
只偷走一幅十元的油划
The only thing he steals is the $ 10 oil painting.
他偷划的目的是什么？
What the hell does he want with that?
有事需要我效劳吗？
Is there something I can help you with?
什么？不需要
What? No.
如果你用购物车装东西 会比较轻松点
You know, it'd be a little easier if you used a cart for all that stuff.
我只是K
I'm just...
想看袋子装不装得下
I wanted to see if it all fit in the bag.
你的膝盖怎么了？
What happened to your knee there?
骑机车出车祸
Motorcycle accident.
所以你的行动不便，对吧？
So you don't move around too well then, do you?
的确
Not really.
-那就好 -嘿K嘿K
- Well, that's good. - Hey, hey. Hey!
你还是可以跟我一起去
You can still come with me.
不，我K
No, I could...
我可以办到的
I could do this.
-如果没办法怎么办？ -我们再会合
- And if you can't? - Then we still meet up.
-所有的计划不变 -去布夏伊布斯
- Exactly where we planned. - Bullshai Booze.
-是波修伊 -波修伊
- Bolshoi. - Bolshoi.
我会带罗杰一起去
L.J.'s gonna be with me.
-你记得怎么去吗？ -我怎么可能忘记
- You remember how to get there? - How can I forget?
周四晚上六点
Thursday night, 6:00.
这是我们最后的机会
It's our last shot.
如果K
If we're...
如果一切顺利 我们就能永远消失
If we do this right, we're gone forever.
三天内要走那么远不容易
A lot of ground to cover in three days.
很不容易
A lot of ground.
好吧
All right.
保重
Take care.
他们会去找你的
They'll be gunning for you.
他们会想尽办法逮捕你，所以K
They'll get you any way they can, so...
好
Yep.
告诉罗杰 我会准备有他名字的冲浪板
Tell L. J... Tell him I said there'll be a surfboard with his name on it.
很好，波修伊布斯见
Nice. Bolshoi Booze.
-三天 -三天
- Three days. - Three days.
别太招摇
Keep your head down.
丹奎迪小姐
Ms. Tancredi.
嗨K
Hi...
我想通知你，法医已经K
...I just want to let you know that the M. A...
完成了初步的验尸
...she's finished her preliminary examination of the body.
她找不到任何他杀的嫌疑
She found no signs of foul play.
我知道你难以接受，但我们也和 驻守在外的警卫谈过
I know it's a shock, but we've also spoken to the detail guard stationed outside.
自从你父亲从华盛顿回来后 除了你父亲之外
And he didn't see anyone, other than your father, enter or exit...
他就没见到其他人进出官邸
...since he came back from Washington.
我父亲不是有自杀倾向的人
My father's not a suicidal man.
有需要帮你联络其他家人吗？
Look, is there any extended family I should call?
我是独生女，我母亲过世了
I'm an only child and my mother passed away.
-让我静一静好吗？ -好的
- Could I have a moment, please? - Yeah.
我给你的条件可遇不可求
That's a hell of a good deal, son.
这次越狱不再另加刑期
I mean, we're talking no additional time on your sentence for the escape.
你要白纸黑字 我可以给你白纸黑字的保证
You want it in writing, I'll put it in writing.
我们会送你去高级监狱
We will put you up at Club Fed.
你每天可以陪 股票经纪人和律师打壁球
You'll spend your days playing racquetball with stockbrokers and lawyers.
四年后你就可以出狱
Four years from now, you'll be on the street.
22岁，毫无前科
Twenty-two years old, with a clean slate...
光明的未来等着你
...and your whole life ahead of you.
人命完全不会怪在你头上
And no blood on your hands.
好吗？
Okay?
房子里有个女人
There's a woman in the house.
如果你们出现
If you guys show up...
他们只会挟持她当人质
...they're just gonna turn her into a hostage.
茶包宁死也不愿回监狱
T-Bag, he ain't coming out alive.
他一定会杀了她
And he's gonna take her with him.
这件事让我来解决
Let me worry about that.
绝对不行
No, hell, no.
只有他们信任的人出现在门前
The only way that that woman comes out free...
才能保住那女人的性命
...is if someone shows up on that porch that they trust.
也就是你
Being you.
就是我
Being me.
我带你去找他们
I'll take you to them.
你K
Oh, you like...
喜欢牛肉干？
You like jerky?
你喜欢牛肉干
You like jerky.
你为何入狱？
What were you in for?
我不想谈，小姐
I don't want to talk, lady.
我在自己家里被囚禁
I'm a prisoner in my own house.
你至少可以和我聊聊吧
The least you could offer me is a little conversation.
好吧
All right.
我猜对时告诉我
Just let me know when I hit it.
谋杀、强奸
Murder. Rape.
绑架、性侵害
Kidnapping. Sexual abuse.
-猥亵儿童 -是重度抢劫
- Child sexual abuse. - Aggravated robbery.
-你的刑期有多久？ -五年
- How long were you doing? - Five years.
你的刑期还剩下多久？
How much longer did you have left to serve?
18个月
Eighteen months.
既然如此，你为何还越狱K
Why on earth would you break out of prison with...?
她叫什么名字？
What's her name?
不重要
Doesn't matter.
怎么？她跟别的男人私奔了？
So, what? She was running away with another man?
-你应该放弃她，没必要K -她怀了我的小孩
- You should've let her go instead of... - she's having my baby.
-预产期是什么时候？ -我不想谈这件事
- How far along is she? - I don't want to talk about it.
我怀孕两个月 周二才第一次照超音波
I'm two months. I just had my first-trimester sonogram on Tuesday.
请传达，调度呼叫各小队
Ten-five, Dispatch to all units,
她有拿照片给你K？
Has she shown you pictures of...?
调查局护送大卫阿普斯基 小队待命
Transporting David Apolskis in FBI custody, Stand by,
我们一整天都挖不完 需要更多人力
Yo, this is gonna take all day. We need more manpower.
你光站在那说废话 土壤也不会自己跳出来
Standing around and jabbering ain't gonna get the dirt out of that ground.
我受够了
All right, that's it.
你这浑蛋，还有话要说吗？
You son of a bitch! Now what?
-我们得走了 -为何？
- We gotta roll. - Why?
无线电上说中间人被逮了
They got Tweener. It was on the radio.
很荣幸认识各位
Nice knowing y'all.
-有提到我们的位置吗？ -我可不想留下来看结果
- They say anything about where we are? - I'm not hanging around to find out.
也许你该留下来
Yo, maybe you should.
Maybe you should.
也许我们都该留下
Maybe we all should.
再解说一次情况 他们都没有武器？
Let's go over this again. None of them were armed?
没有枪
Guns? No.
包威有把螺丝起子
Bagwell had a screwdriver or something.
-有必要这样吗？ -有必要
- Do we really need this, man? - Yeah.
以免你做傻事 例如通知他们我来了
In case you decide to do something stupid, like tip them off.
你没有意见吧？
You don't have a problem with that, do you?
罗盘，确认
Compass, check.
地图，确认，绳索，确认
Map, check. Rope, check.
好
Okay.
你一定很纳闷 我们来密西根湖做什么吧？
I bet you're wondering what we're doing down here by Lake Michigan, huh?
因为只要往那边一直走 就能抵达海洋
It's because if you go far enough that way, you get to the ocean.
你知道外面是什么地方吗？
You know what's out there.
荷兰
Holland.
我们要住在风车里
We're gonna live in a windmill.
我们只需要一艘木筏
All we need is a raft.
我要做一艘木筏
I'm gonna build it.
就从K
All starts with this...
不，这根树枝开始
No, this stick.
查理威莫兰，愿上帝保佑你 还有你的老旧麻袋
Charles Westmoreland, God bless you and your wrinkled old sack.
钱全在这里
It's all here.
我真要好好感激你，帅哥
I owe you a profound thanks, Pretty.
几天之后
Couple of days from now...
我就会口袋塞满百万美金 走在曼谷街头
...I'm gonna be walking the streets of Bangkok with a million U.s.
这等于四千万泰铢
That's about 40 million baht in the local currency.
你为什么那么喜欢泰国？
What the hell is up with you and Thailand, huh?
黑市手术、匿名移植捐赠者
Black-market surgery, anonymous transplant donors.
还有人妖，能不喜欢吗？
Hes dressed like shes. What's there not to like?
你真的想把手掌换掉？
Are you really gonna try to replace that hand?
我的身体会排斥这手掌
Body ain't taking to this one.
-可恶 -我们动作要快
- Unbelievable. - All right, let's move.
那只手不会是白人的手
You know, that hand ain't gonna be white.
-什么？ -你的新手掌
- What? - The new one.
就算你到了泰国 也不会有白人的手
Even if you get down there, it ain't gonna be white.
这个种族歧视的人 会有只亚洲人的手掌
Hey, Johnny KKK over here's gonna have an Asian hand.
不准出错，逮捕所有人
No mistakes. Let's get them clean.
我要知道我是否能信任你
I need to know if I can trust you.
他们打算越狱
They're escaping,
你不能就这样丢下我不管
No, you can't leave me here,
-不能这样 -我们说好了，记得吗？
- Not like this, - We had a deal, remember?
请你离开
Now walk.
-史考特 -我的时间不多
- Scott. - I don't got much time, all right?
我有话要告诉你
I had to tell you something,
那天你在汽车旅馆为我做的事
What you did for me that day at the motel...
我这一生 从来没有人对我这么好
Ain't nobody in my life that's been to bat for me like that.
-逮住他，快 -我欺骗了你
- Get him. Go, go, go! - And I lied to you, okay?
我的名字不是史考特
My name ain't scott.
-我叫大卫 -天啊
- My name's Dave. - Oh, my God.
-大卫阿普斯基 -快上K
- David Apolskis. - Go now, go!
-离开门边 -马上跪下
- Get away from the door! - Get down. Now!
-双手抱头 -我只想说K
- Put your hands on your head! - And I just...
带回车上
Put him in the car.
我想告诉你，我会写信给你
I wanted you to know, all right, I'm gonna be writing to you.
我很希望你可以回信
And I sure as hell hope that you write back.
安全了
All clear!
有可以效劳的地方吗？
Can I help you?
抱歉，你是谁？
I'm sorry. Do I know you?
我是承包商，电力出了问题
Contractor. Got some electrical issues.
你帮不了我的忙
No, you can't help me.
不好意思，有问题吗？
Excuse me, is there a problem?
-欧文斯小姐？ -她不在家
- Ms. Owens? - She's not home.
我应该要来载她去俱乐部K
Yeah, well, I'm supposed to drive her to the club for...
她已经去俱乐部了
she already went to the club.
对，她出来了 说她要去俱乐部
Yeah, she came out, said she was going to the club.
她上了车就走了
She got in her car and left.
我知道的就是这么多
I don't know what else to tell you.
好吧，谢谢
Yeah. Okay, thanks.
他走了，可是我们得马上离开 因为他一到俱乐部
He's gone, but we gotta get out of here, because once he gets to the club...
就会发现她不在 到时他就会回来
...he's gonna find out she's not there and he's gonna be back.
你知道吗？你说的对
You know what? You were right.
一吐为快的感觉的确很好
It does feel good to get stuff off your chest.
抱歉我骗了你
I'm sorry I had to play you like that, bro.
你要做什么？
Yo, what's up?
来吧，路程很远
Come on. It's gonna be a long drive.
下车走走吧
Stretch your legs.
好吧
All right.
凯勒曼 你不是要处理罗杰柏劳的事
Kellerman, I thought you were gonna deal with the L, J, Burrows situation,
我办好了
oh, I did.
那他为何明天会被释放？
Then why is he being released from custody?
这小孩本身对我们毫无用处
In and of himself, the kid is useless to us.
让人来找他 对我们才有价值
His only value is in who comes looking for him.
比尔，更重要的是K
More importantly, Bill.
丹奎迪州长 他不在我们的计划之中
Governor Tancredi, Not part of our plan,
据我所知，你杀的人也不少
Last time I checked, you left no shortage of bodies in your wake.
为了卡洛琳的地位 我不得不这么做
No, I did what I had to do to get Caroline where she is.
既然她已经升官了 我们就没必要引人侧目
Now that she's there, let's not draw any more attention than we have to.
你以为往上爬的过程 才是最艰难的？
You think getting to the top is the hard part?
她现在是全世界的注目焦点 敌人多了几百倍
She's a hundred times more visible. Has a hundred times more enemies.
任何知道一点风声的人 都要处理掉
Anyone who knows anything has got to be dealt with,
只要有人造成威胁 他们就得死
If someone is a liability, they go.
丹奎迪已经造成威胁
Tancredi was becoming a liability.
他的女儿也是
So is his daughter.
等等，什么？
Wait. What?
莎拉？
Sara?
再见，保罗
Goodbye, Paul.
（伊利诺州，芝加哥）
（注射用吗啡）
你现在和他们一起逃走
You walk out with those guys now...
迟早会被逮捕的 这你应该清楚吧？
...it's only a matter of time before you get caught. You realize that?
你不光要面对越狱的刑责
You're not just dealing with escape charges.
还有攻击、非法挟持、绑架K
Assault, unlawful imprisonment, kidnapping...
-我现在不想听 -你应该听
- I don't need to hear this. - No, you do.
你认为你能p遥法外多久？
How much longer do you really think you can stay ahead of the cops?
如果你自首K
Look, if you turn yourself in...
我会出庭作证 我会说你愿意合作
...I will testify at the sentencing, I will say that you cooperated.
-这会有很大的帮助 -闭嘴
- That can make a difference. - Shut up.
聪明一点
Be smart.
你的小孩即将出生 你要看着他满2岁K
You have a baby on the way. Wanna be around for its second birthday?
-还是22岁生日？ -闭嘴
- Or its 22nd? - Shut up.
如果你不想听 自己的大错特错
If you didn't wanna hear what a big mistake you were making...
你早该堵住我的嘴K
...you would've put that gag back on...
费南多，我们该走了
Fernando! It's time to go!
现在回头还来得及，费南多
You can still do the right thing, Fernando.
你瞧瞧K
Hey, looky here.
你瞧瞧
Looky here.
给你零用钱 让你住大饭店时给服务生小费
Pocket change, in case you wanna tip the valet when you're at the Ritz.
这才像话，苏克在哪里？
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about, boy. Where's sucre?
在这里
Right here.
你要做什么？
What are you doing?
把袋子放下
Drop the bag.
你们休想离开
No one's going anywhere.
我告诉你K
Hey, yo.
你该知道，我不会背叛他们的
Just so you know, man, I'm not gonna roll on those guys.
如果你是为了这件事 我是不会说的K
It ain't gonna happen, so if that's what this is about...
我们之前聊过告解
We were talking about confession earlier.
然后K
And...
我想我欠你一次道歉，因为我说谎
I think I owe you an apology because I lied to you...
关于奥斯卡席尔斯
...about oscar shales.
那浑蛋一直逼我
Smart-ass just kept pushing it.
于是我当场失控
I snapped.
就是这里
Right there.
我从这里开枪射他
That's where I put the bullet in him.
这不关我的事
I don't care about none of this.
那次我做错了 因为鉴识组会查明真相
Mistake about that is that forensics will tell the whole tale.
我的枪抵在他头上 造成火药烫伤
Powder burns. The gun was right against his head.
先生K
Sir...
-我觉得我们该K -告解就有这种好处
- We should go back... - That's what's good about confession.
你一吐为快，把事情说出来
Because you say something, you get it off your chest...
接着全世界都会知道
...and it just goes out there into the whole world.
我真的很抱歉，小伙子 希望你能谅解
I'm so sorry about this, kid, because I hope you understand.
-等等K -我对你没有成见
- Yo, yo, hold on... - I got nothing against you, kid.
你要做什么？
What are you doing, man?
但他们有
But they do.